



Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement

Analysis, Solution

Architecture, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, iQuery, PHP, Laravel, CodeIgniter

Framework, JSON, XML.



Current Designation: Software Engineer -UI Development Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Current Company: STRAVISO INDIA PVT. LTD. Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Pune, Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application

Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution

Architecture, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter Framework, JSON, XML

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Modified: 21-Jan-21 Last Active: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Energetic software developer with 4.5 years of experience in developing, UI designing and deployment robust code for highvolume businesses by the web-based application.

Proficient knowledge and working experience in Web Technology (Html, CSS, Bootstrap, Java Script, jQuery), PHP, Codelgniter, Laravel, Restful Web Services and MySQL-DB.

Ability to learn and adapt quickly to the emerging new technologies.

Work Experience

STRAVISO INDIA PVT. LTD. as Software Engineer -UI Development

Dec 2019 to Till Date

Researching, designing, implementing and managing software programs.

Identifying areas for modification in existing programs and subsequently developing these modifications.

Writing and implementing efficient UI and Backend code.

Maintaining and upgrading existing systems.

Working closely with other developers, UI designers, business and systems analysts.

CHATE GLOBAL SERVICES as Software Engineer

Mar 2017 to Oct 2019

Researching, designing, implementing and managing software programs.

Identifying areas for modification in existing programs and subsequently developing these modifications.

Writing and implementing efficient UI and Backend code.

Maintaining and upgrading existing systems.

Working closely with other developers, UI designers, business and systems analysts.

Testing and evaluating new programs.

Miiint Solutions as Software Developer

Aug 2016 to Feb 2017

1/22/2021

Researching, designing, implementing and managing software programs.

Identifying areas for modification in existing programs and subsequently developing these modifications.

Writing and implementing efficient UI and Backend code.

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from Tilak Maharashtra University in 2012

PG: MCA (Computers) from University of Pune, Pune in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
HTML, CSS			
BOOTSTRAP			
JavaScript, JQuery			
PHP, Laravel			
codelgniter Framework			
Restful Web Service			
JSON, XML			
MySQL			
Linux, Windows			
VS CODE IDE			
MySQL-workbench			
postman			
Microsoft Office			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time